FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
Joo.
Would you like something to drink?
You did a great job.
You too, sir.
Working with you again felt like old times.
I could really count on you.
Me too.
What did you think of Jin Isoo?
He can be a bit odd,
And he's unpredictable,
But he's got good instincts.
And he's quite serious about the job.
Right?
He's actually a decent detective.
Do you have someone lined up to lead Team 1?
No.
No one.
So I was wondering...
Someone just like you would be perfect for the job.
Someone who's capable,
Can manage Detective Jin, and has real charisma.
Someone of that caliber
Is really hard to come by.
Hello!
When did you have time to make these?
Hi there! Want a photo?
He's going overboard again.
Come on, it's all good fun.
Okay, band.
Let's give it a try.
Just like we practiced. Ready!
-  Stop! -  What in the world...
What is all this?
Sir!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
- That good for nothing... - Sir.
Come on, clear all this out.
- This was Jin Isoo's doing. - Sir!
It's for my new boss. You know the drill.
Let's do this.
Somebody's working hard.
Of course. We're getting a new team leader.
Of course.
Oh. Incoming!
Joo Hyera?
I didn't expect such a grand welcome.
Detective Jin has been busy since this morning.
I guess you can be sweet.
This is the new team leader of Violent Crime Investigation Team 1, Joo Hyera. :cue
She's got years on you boys.
She was on our Violent Crime Team before moving to Counterterrorism.
Detective Jin, take good care of your new boss.
Take good care of her.
Detective Jin Isoo,
Detective Park Junyoung, Detective Choi Kyungjin.
Glad to join the team.
This has to be a nightmare.
It's real.
Get used to it.
Looking forward to it, nutjob.
But why?
She has it good in Counterterrorism, so why, huh?
That's true.
Why the sudden transfer?
I'm seriously doomed.
What are you talking about?
She's a capable, experienced veteran detective.
We don't get along.
She doesn't like me.
Nutjob. Hey, nutjob.
Hey, nutjob!
Hey, nutjob.
It's nothing new.
I didn't like you at first, either.
Sir!
What?
So...
About Detective Joo Hyera.
I heard she worked here before.
Yeah.
We worked together for about a year or so.
Then why did she come back here?
Beats me.
Ah.
It must be to torment you.
Come on, be serious!
She's good at her job.
She's pretty laid-back, so don't worry.
How old is she?
Same age as you, I think.
- Same age as me? - Yes.
By the way, don't ever make bets with her.
- Why not? - She's kind of competitive...
No, she's insanely competitive.
She always has to win.
Hmm...
Yes, come in.
Oh, Detective Joo Hyera. Come in and have a seat.
I appreciate you taking on this tough role.
Not at all.
You also successfully closed the bombing case.
We're lucky to have you.
You're too kind.
By the way, I have one favor to ask of you.
Of course. Please, go ahead.
It's about Jin Isoo.
I can't sleep at night because of him.
Strictly speaking,
Those bombings wouldn't have happened if it weren't for him.
What's a spoiled rich kid doing running wild in the police force?
God knows what he did, but he won over everyone in Violent Crime and Chief Park.
Discipline's gone to hell around here.
Discipline's important in an organization.
Which is why
You should watch him, and when he's about to cause trouble,
Report it to me. I'll use it to kick him out.
Yes, sir.
Good. I'm counting on you.
I also have a favor to ask.
Yes, what is it?
Once Jin Isoo leaves,
I'd like to pick his replacement.
Sure, you do that.
Yes, sir. :cue
Detective Jin.
Got something to say?
Nope.
We can finish the report tomorrow.
Let's go out for drinks tonight.
Okay.
Then I know this celebrity chef...
Let's go somewhere local, in one hour.
Yes, ma'am.
She's the worst. Seriously, the worst.
The absolute worst.
Okay, let's make a toast.
Bro.
- Here's to working together. - Welcome to the team!
- Welcome. -  Welcome.
Chief Park? He was my immediate supervisor.
Wow! What was he like?
He was scary.
I learned a lot from him.
We heard so much about you.
- Like how you caught Kim Dusik. - Kim Dusik?
Yeah, a serial robber and killer.
I heard you spent a week on stakeout.
People still talk about that?
Of course.
A whole week? Where?
The convenience store in front of his girlfriend's house.
I worked there.
I caught him when he came to buy cigarettes at dawn.
But...
...why did you come back?
That's...
No comment.
"No comment," my foot.
- Bro, where are you going? -  The restroom.
Then, tell us about the chief.
The chief?
What kind of stuff?
Something cool, or something dirty?
Something dirty.
It was summer, around five years ago.
It was a scorching hot day.
It turns out that bastard
Was hiding in a pigsty.
The chief just dove right in.
No way.
The chief?
The stench was unbearable, but we couldn't say a word.
His wife told him at the door to strip down and throw it all away.
I didn't expect that from him.
We didn't order these.
Ah. Over there.
No way!
SCORE OVER 1,000 FOR 4 FREE BEERS
Isoo scored over 1,000 points.
This isn't something just anyone can do.
"Just anyone?"
You haven't seen the champion's photo yet?
Champion?
DART CHAMPION
- Ooh. - That's amazing.
Champion?
I'm taking that champion's place today.
- Ooh. - Oh!
Great shot!
Talk is cheap.
So cool. :cue
Please could you stop them?
We're sorry.
You stepped on the line.
Okay, fine.
I thought he said they don't get along.
They get along really well.
Oh!
Detective Joo won.
No wonder she's the dart champion. Now, let's go.
- Come on. -  Great shot!
- Bro. - Let's go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh!
The machine was so shocked, it broke.
Let's go. Come on.
Bro.
Learn to accept defeat.
Come on.
Let's go.
Huh?
Ah, I'm a really great shot, too.
As great as me?
Learn to accept the results.
That's a tiny kitten.
Just one more round.
One round.
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Mmm.
Morning.
Goodness, look at you.
What time did you go home?
Around 3:00 a.m.
Detective Joo must be really tired, too.
Good morning.
Ma'am, are you all right?
Mmm? What do you mean?
Let's finish that report today.
- Yes, ma'am. - Understood.
:cue
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
AHIN
AHIN THERE'S A GHOST IN THE ABANDONED HOUSE!
"Whatever it is, I'll take care of it."
You startled me.
DETECTIVE JIN RESPONDING!
You think you're Batman? Light a signal, why don't you?
Oh, I do give off that Batman vibe.
That's narcissism. It's a disorder, you know.
You probably don't know, but I'm the cheat code for solving cases.
You should really see me out there in the field.
I believe I did.
Frozen, after touching the bomb.
What's the report about?
There's a ghost in the abandoned house.
My name is Park Ahin. I'm a middle school student from Gangha 3-dong.
My dream is to become a great police officer.
That's why I have a habit of keeping an eye out for anything suspicious.
But a few days ago,
I saw these eerie lights floating inside the abandoned house across the street.
There was a murder there, so the house hasn't sold in years.
I'm sure it's some kind of vengeful ghost.
It's asking us to catch the killer.
How will you take care of this?
I'll check it out first.
Mmm. To arrest a ghost?
Or perform an exorcism?
What if there's actually something there, huh?
You can't just brush off a tip, damn it.
By the way, you're straight-up talking down to me now.
I mean, well,
We're the same rank now,
And the same age.
And you're not my instructor anymore.
Do what you want. Who am I to stop a nutjob?
- Let's head over there. - What?
Let's go check it out.
Aren't you clocking out?
I've got nothing to do at home.
Forget it. I'm going alone.
I should come with you.
What if a ghost latches onto you?
Come on.
Let's take your car.
Why? What is it this time?
Then we can take my bike and you hang on to my waist.
No, we can just go separately.
Come on, don't be so heartless.
I want to ride in a car like this, too.
Open the door.
Ooh.
Nice car.
Off we go.
:cue
FOR SALE
It's eerie.
Is this a haunted house or something?
Oh, my God.
They actually came.
Ahin, come out for dinner.
I'm not eating.
The body was here.
Do you know what kind of case it was?
No.
There was a struggle,
And they resisted until the end,
But were eventually killed and became ghosts?
You believe that?
- Ghosts and stuff? - No.
I would if I saw one, but I never have.
I like horror movies, though. You?
I don't watch that stuff.
So you get scared easily.
Of course not.
I just find them boring, that's all.
Why bother watching that?
Oh, come on!
Really boring, isn't it?
You check upstairs.
I'll check this side.
She's seriously annoying.
Oh!
Meow.
:cue
-  Park Ahin. -  I said I'm not eating.
Don't you dare make noodles at midnight again.
Okay, fine. I'm busy.
- What on earth are you watching with-- - Please just...
Good luck making it to the academy.
Just get out.
Goodness, what are you...
Park Ahin!
Detective Jin.
Jin Isoo!
Nutjob!
Yes, ma'am!
- What's this? - Jin Isoo.
Snap out of it.
I'm completely awake.
What's going on?
- Hey, what happened? - I don't know.
I got attacked out of nowhere.
Hey, try to untie this.
Okay.
I actually have pretty long fingers.
I got it.
- That's my finger. - Oh.
Thought it was a rope.
Stop messing around. We could die here.
No one's going to die.
Why are you being so dramatic?
We don't know who attacked us.
Okay, fine.
Just stay still, will you?
What is it?
Nothing. It's nothing.
No need to be alarmed. Stay calm.
Stay calm.
Why is this being so difficult?
Hey, I smell something burning.
She's got a good nose.
Is there a fire?
Kind of. No, it's fine. We're okay for now.
Hey, Jin Isoo.
I'm working on it! Jeez.
Do you see that broken glass over there?
Yeah.
On three, fall left.
Left? Okay.
One, two,
Three.
It was my right.
You need to be more specific.
Again. One...
- Two, three! - Two, three!
Get up.
- Get up. - One, two, three.
Again. One, two, three.
- Where is it? - Go up.
A bit farther.
Got it.
Be careful.
Don't move. You'll get hurt.
Fire.
It's a fire.
Yes, this is Violent Crime Team 1.
There's a fire. :cue
The detectives went inside, but now it's on fire.
How do we get out?
Like this.
Get out of the way.
Ladies first.
If it weren't for me,
You would've burned to death in that house.
It would've been the end.
Detective Joo, just stay close to me from now on.
The hero never dies that easily.
You want to live?
Then just stick close to me, okay?
Okay.
What do we do now?
Do we jump, or not?
- Like this? - What?
Nutjob, you okay?
Yeah. I seriously almost died.
You should've told me we were jumping. Look how high that is.
The hero never dies that easily.
Stay close to me if you want to live.
There really is something here.
I have great instincts, huh?
Oh, you're bleeding.
I'm fine.
Come on.
Give it here.
- Aah! - You said you were fine.
You're tying it too tight, so it hurts.
It's to stop the bleeding.
You shouldn't have gone overboard.
That's my thing.
Jin Isoo!
- Bro! -  There they are again.
Are you okay?
I'm not, but don't make a fuss.
Are you okay, Detective Joo?
Yes.
What happened?
It was arson.
Someone tied us up and set a fire.
Detective!
Oh.
Who is this?
I'm so sorry. I didn't see anything because I was eating noodles.
Ah, you must be Ahin.
Are you okay?
Huh?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Have we met somewhere before?
:cue
- Take a video of the onlookers. - Yes, ma'am.
How did you end up here?
We got a report.
What kind of report?
That middle schooler reported that someone keeps entering an empty house.
We came to check just in case.
Did you see who attacked you?
They came up from behind.
Without knowing who you were?
Yeah.
It's not some punk squatting in an empty house.
There's something going on here.
What is this?
Guys, come here. Quickly.
Let's open it up.
The padlock is too new for a long-abandoned house.
Look. Someone tried to pry it open.
That?
There's definitely something in there.
Some kind of dark secret.
I told you, I've got great instincts.
You two know that.
Get a search warrant.
Why would we need a warrant? We almost died.
That's not enough.
We'll say it was on fire.
We can't.
Kyungjin.
Hey, come on.
If you open it now, whatever we find inside will be inadmissible.
You know the drill.
But...
By the way,
Why do you keep talking casually to our team leader?
I told her I'd be respectful, but she kept telling me to relax.
Goodness.
She's super chill.
Honestly.
Don't open it. Don't you dare.
Ah...
Detective Joo, are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine, sir.
What happened?
We don't know yet.
I think we need to do some more digging on this house.
Okay. I've sent the forensics team, so wrap it up and go home.
Sir.
We found a suspicious basement here.
But it's locked with a padlock.
Can we get a warrant?
We need to know what kind of case this is to request a warrant.
Why? You think it has something to do with the fire?
I'm not sure.
In that case,
Investigate first, then get a warrant if you need to.
Yes, sir.
- We'll have to see about the warrant. - Okay.
The fire started on the first floor,
Then appears to have spread up the stairs.
I heard there was a murder here a long time ago,
But someone's been in and out since then.
Okay. We'll look for any recent traces.
We'll go collect security footage from the streets nearby.
Okay.
- Let's go. - Okay.
-  Jin Isoo! -  Hey! :cue
- What are you doing? - I told you not to.
Hey!
Is it illegal for a homeowner to break down his own door?
No way.
I bought this house.
You bought it?
The realtor's number was on the front gate.
FOR SALE
The owner asked them to sell it no matter what.
So you just bought it?
Wow, bro.
Who just spends money like that...
Except you, of course.
You know how to flex.
Mmm.
So this is your cheat code.
This is nothing to be surprised about.
You're pretty timid.
Where did you get that hammer?
I borrowed it from Ahin. They're repairing their wall.
All right, then.
Now, don't be shy.
Welcome.
Detective Joo.
That looks newly covered.
Kyungjin.
Stand back.
Detective Joo.
GANGHA 3-DONG BURIED BODIES CASE
How did you end up going to that house?
We received a tip.
What kind of tip?
Someone reported that there was a ghost.
To me.
Hey, what is he talking about? Did he just say a ghost?
It was a report of lights in an empty house.
We went to check if it was being used for criminal activity.
Okay, fine.
Why did you open the basement? I said wait.
I went ahead and bought the house!
I see.
You bought the house.
Right, so,
You uncovered five bodies?
Yes, they're performing the autopsy now.
ONE BODY, BURIED RECENTLY
Four of them are skeletal remains, so identifying them will take a while.
For now,
Team 1 and 2 will both be on this case.
Make sure this doesn't leak to the press,
And identify the victims quickly. Got it?
- Yes, sir. -  Yes, sir.
:cue
Let's begin the autopsy.
I investigated the murder that happened inside the house.
Around 1:00 a.m. on October 25, 2016,
A couple and their son, a college student, were all murdered.
There were no signs of forced entry,
But cash and jewelry were gone,
So it was suspected to be a robbery-homicide,
But the culprit was never caught.
It's a cold case.
No fingerprints, no hair.
Not a single trace was left behind.
So the house was abandoned after that, and then it was used as a burial site.
By the serial killer.
Detective Joo.
The most recently deceased victim
Had these glasses in their pants.
I'll go check it out.
Okay. We'll go after the arsonist.
Got it. Let's go.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
- Let's check the footage from the scene. - Okay.
Stop.
That's the guy. The black hoodie.
- Track him. - Okay.
It's a rental.
- Run the plate. - Got it.
Excuse me.
We're with the police.
How can I help you?
Could you tell us
Where you supplied these glasses?
I'll check right away.
DOHYUN CAR RENTAL
Who rented this car?
Oh, that car hasn't been returned yet.
One moment, please.
Oh...
It's that car there.
Right.
Hey, hey.
Police.
Please come out, serial killer.
Careful. He could be armed.
You're right.
Come out.
Or we'll break it.
JEONG DAEUN GANGHA 3-DONG ARSON SUSPECT
Inside that abandoned house,
Did you attack us?
What?
Did you knock us out and tie us up?
No, how would I even do that?
Last night, you were at the abandoned house
At 14-1 Gangha 3-dong, right?
Yes.
I started the fire.
We almost burned to death.
My team leader hurt her arm. :cue
I'm really sorry. I didn't know there were people inside.
Why did you start the fire?
Because Hyeonsu disappeared,
And no one will believe me.
Please start from the beginning.
Hyeonsu is a lawyer.
We've been dating for three years,
And we were about to get married.
4 MONTHS AGO
JEONG DAEUN'S FIANCÉ PARK HYEONSU
-  It's raining. - Hold on.
- What? - It's raining so suddenly.
Let's go.
He was a really kind person.
When we were busy planning our wedding,
He said something important had come up.
His former classmate was in trouble and needed his help.
Not long after, she was murdered.
But then I was told
That Hyeonsu was the killer.
I kept saying he'd never do something like that,
But no one would believe me.
They said all the evidence was there,
That she and Hyeonsu used to date,
That he stalked her to get back with her, then killed her.
But that doesn't make any sense.
Sir.
What is it?
PARK HYEONSU
Then why did you go to that house?
Hyeonsu installed a location-sharing app on my phone.
This app will show you where I am.
We can't see each other very often.
Now, if you just check the app, you'll know where I'm working.
Oh, you.
On the day of the murder,
Hyeonsu's last location was that house.
At first, I was too shaken and forgot all about the app.
When I later checked and went to his last location,
It was an abandoned house.
Hyeonsu has no connection to that neighborhood.
Wait, so,
You went in there alone?
Weren't you scared?
I asked the police to investigate,
But the detective in charge wouldn't listen.
But there was a strange basement there.
I tried to open it...
...but I couldn't.
So I set the place on fire,
Thinking they might find something while putting it out.
I honestly didn't know someone was inside.
By any chance,
Did you see anyone suspicious there?
No, no one.
Jiwon.
Hi.
Have you eaten at all?
No.
I wasn't really hungry.
I got you a sandwich.
Thanks.
I'll eat it later.
Did you find anything?
We start work on the skeletal remains tomorrow morning.
We performed the autopsy on the most recent victim first...
...but the body's too decomposed to recover any fingerprints.
Look here. There are three stab wounds.
And the wrists have marks that appear to be from duct tape.
So the victim was stabbed while tied up?
Yes. :cue
DETECTIVE DIVISION
You? Against me?
That's ridiculous.
It's him.
The detective who wouldn't believe me.
Sir, how did this happen?
We didn't make a mistake.
INVESTIGATION REPORT
Three months ago, in Yuseon-dong,
Kim Minseo was murdered.
- Hello. - Hello.
The suspect fled on a motorcycle,
Entered Park Hyeonsu's house...
...then drove away in his car.
Even so,
Would a man about to get married,
Who was sharing his location with his girlfriend,
Plan and execute a murder?
It doesn't make sense.
What was his motive?
Park Hyeonsu kept texting her, asking to meet up.
Did you take care of it?
I'll be waiting, so tell me when you're done.
If you keep this up, I'm not holding back.
Please meet me just once.
You want to see me lose it?
Kim Minseo kept refusing.
Kim Minseo
Had filed a stalking complaint before.
Park Hyeonsu's fingerprints were on a knife found at the scene.
That knife was the knife missing from Park Hyeonsu's house.
We also found the disguise he used as a courier inside his house.
We confirmed the weapon, fingerprints, motive, and movements.
Then he suddenly disappeared, so we put him on the wanted list.
But...
These belong to Park Hyeonsu.
Got the autopsy results?
They'll do the rest tomorrow, so this is just the most recent victim's.
A male in his 30s. Died three months ago, and stabbed to death while bound.
Wait, so,
The murder suspect you were after three months ago
Was murdered and his body was found at the abandoned house?
Did someone get revenge on him?
Does Kim Minseo have any family?
Her husband and her parents.
How can you find and kill someone even the police couldn't find?
What about the abandoned house? Did he even go there?
His phone went offline near there and never came back online.
His car was found abandoned at Incheon Port.
We assumed he'd snuck out of the country by sea,
So we had Interpol issue a Red Notice.
Let's verify this first. :cue
Ask them to compare the body's DNA with Park Hyeonsu's.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Yes, understood.
Yes, come in.
Detective Joo, have a seat.
I'm going fishing at dawn.
If I catch some big ones, would you like one?
They don't call me the Sea King's eldest son for nothing.
I'm all right, thank you.
So,
I hear Jin Isoo bought a house.
Yes, sir.
And you found five bodies inside?
Does he just make trouble wherever he goes?
- Is there nothing wrong with that? - Pardon?
I mean, is there anything we can find fault with?
Can a police officer just buy up a house like that?
There's no reason he can't.
He's not breaking the law.
We found five bodies there
And prevented it from becoming the perfect crime,
So it's a good thing.
How is that a good thing?
Come on,
I just want to make it to retirement in peace, for God's sake.
Should we hand this over to Seoul Headquarters?
It's a big case.
Don't worry, sir. We'll catch whoever's behind this.
NO USABLE FINGERPRINTS
SUSPECT, VICTIM
PARK HYEONSU, AGE 34 KIM MINSEO, AGE 34
VICTIM KIM MINSEO'S HOUSE
SUSPECT PARK HYEONSU'S HOUSE
Ma'am, we got a match on the DNA.
It is Park Hyeonsu.
AUTOPSY REPORT
Who could have killed Park Hyeonsu?
Don't just think about him.
There are five bodies killed by the same guy.
Then, was Park Hyeonsu
Murdered by a serial killer?
No, wait.
Let's start over.
What if Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one who killed Kim Minseo?
You're saying they're professionals?
Yes.
If Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one who killed Kim Minseo...
It's the perfect crime.
Right? Here, look.
Look. The target.
A victim to frame as the suspect.
If they kill the target and the suspect,
Then make him go missing,
The case cannot be solved.
Five perfect crimes.
You need at least two people to make this possible.
They're methodical and cold.
Park Hyeonsu would've been first,
Since they sent those texts.
First, they overpowered Park Hyeonsu.
One of them would've kept watch.
They sent the harassing messages.
- Hello. - Hello, delivery.
Then, after killing the target...
...they dressed up as Park Hyeonsu. :cue
Help me!
Then they buried him and disappeared.
So they're professional killers?
Yes.
They must've been hired to do it.
Those bastards completely fooled me.
We need to start this case over.
The ones who attacked you and Isoo must be the real culprits.
If they came to the house...
It means they killed someone else.
They were there to bury the body.
Wait.
It's blood.
KILLER 1 JANG JAECHUN
It leaked.
KILLER 2 JO BEOMKI
What do we do?
This is bad.
Taegwang.
FLEX X COP 2 EPISODE 3
THE KILLER OF KILLERS YU TAEGWANG
Special Cast. Lee Hakju, Park Soi
We got a new job. Where are you?
I got their location.
I need the chopper.
This is straight out of a soap opera.
You're Korean, right?
- I don't know. - You don't know?
- Freeze. - We're flying out at dawn.
They're ruthless killers, so civilians could get hurt.
Beomki!
If we want to catch them...
Let's hire them to kill someone.
Is this how you normally investigate?
I won't let you down.
You were a real scumbag.
We all go down together.
So the perp's still here.
Jin Isoo!
Who is that?
Did we arrest a gang boss?
Is that Park?
Gosh.
What are they doing?
I have no idea, sir.
Our district
Is just strange overall.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee